const HOLOCRON = [

	{	question: 'Who said “When 900 years old you reach, look as good, you will not, hmm?”',
		answers: [
			'Obi-wan Kenobi',
			'The Emperor',
			'Qui-Gon Jinn',
			'Yoda'],
   correctAnswer: 'Yoda'
	},

	{	question: 'Who is Princess Leia insulting when she says “Why, you stuck up, half-witted, scruffy-looking, Nerf-herder!”',
		answers: [
			'Lando Calrissian',
			'Han Solo',
			'Poe Dameron',
			'Grand Moff Tarkin'],
		correctAnswer: 'Han Solo'
	},

	{	question: 'What place is Obi-Wan Kenobi describing when he says “You will never find a more wretched hive of scum and villainy.”',
		answers: [
			'Mos Eisley',
			'The Death Star',
			'His cave on Tatooine',
			'A clone trooper locker room'],
		correctAnswer: 'Mos Eisley'
	},

	{	question: 'When Leia says to Han Solo “I love you”, how does he respond?',
		answers: [
			'“My beloved, I also love you.”',
			'“Thank you, your worship!”',
			'“I know.”',
			'“You’re ok, I guess.”'],
		correctAnswer: '“I know.”'
	},

	{	question: 'Finish this phrase of Jedi wisdom from Yoda: “Do or do not.”',
		answers: [
			'“There is no try.”',
			'“Care not, I do.”',
			'“Lift the X-Wing from the mud, I shall.”',
			'“Done in 5 minutes, my lunch is.”'],
		correctAnswer: '“There is no try.”'
	},

	{	question: 'Which movie has the Rebel Admiral Ackbar yell “It’s a trap!”?',
		answers: [
			'Empire Strikes Back',
			'The Last Jedi',
			'Return of the Jedi',
			'Rogue One'],
		correctAnswer: 'Return of the Jedi'
	},

	{	question: 'Which character asks his subordinates, incredulously, “Are we blind?!”?',
		answers: [
			'Grand Moff Tarkin',
			'Director Krennic',
			'Kylo Ren',
			'Darth Vader'],
		correctAnswer: 'Director Krennic'
	},

	{	question: 'Whom does Yoda tell that “Fear is the path to the dark side. Fear leads to anger. Anger leads to hate. Hate leads to suffering.”?',
		answers: [
			'Luke Skywalker',
			'Rey',
			'Leia Organa',
			'Anakin Skywalker'],
		correctAnswer: 'Anakin Skywalker'
	},

	{	question: 'Who said this threatening statement: “Now, young Skywalker, you will die.”?',
		answers: [
			'The Emperor',
			'Count Dooku',
			'Darth Maul',
			'General Grievous'],
		correctAnswer: 'The Emperor'
	},

	{	question: 'Which statement said by Darth Vader to Luke Skywalker in Empire Strikes Back causes Luke to say “No, NO!, That’s not true! THAT’S IMPOSSIBLE!”?',
		answers: [
			'“I am your mother.”',
			'“I am your great uncle.”',
			'“I am your father.”',
			'“Lightsabers can’t melt steel beams.”'],
		correctAnswer: '“I am your father.”'
  }
  ];